[
    {
        "source":"",
        "question": "Famous artist Pablo Picasso belongs to which country?",
        "choice1": "Spain",
        "choice2": "Italy",
        "choice3": "France",
        "choice4": "Portugal",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "source":"",
        "question": "Leonardo da Vinci was one of the leading artists of the High Renaissance, from which country?",
        "choice1": "Spain",
        "choice2": "Ireland",
        "choice3": "Portugal",
        "choice4": "Italy",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "source":"",
        "question": "Which animal is treated the cleanest?",
        "choice1": "Whale",
        "choice2": "Pigs",
        "choice3": "Giraffe",
        "choice4": "Zebra",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "source":"",
        "question": "What is the rarest bug in the world?",
        "choice1": "Panda ant",
        "choice2": "Title Beetle",
        "choice3": "Land/ Tree lobster",
        "choice4": "Karner butterfly",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "source":"",
        "question": "What is the hardest sport in the world?",
        "choice1": "Karate",
        "choice2": "Water Polo",
        "choice3": "Weight Lifting",
        "choice4": "Archery",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "source":"",
        "question": "What is the oldest sport?",
        "choice1": "Wrestling",
        "choice2": "Kabadi",
        "choice3": "Bull Fight",
        "choice4": "Cockfight",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "source":"",
        "question": "What animal is lazy?",
        "choice1": "Tree weta",
        "choice2": "The panda ant",
        "choice3": "Red-fanged funnel spider",
        "choice4": "Sloths",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "source":"",
        "question": "What is the world’s heaviest insect?",
        "choice1": "Stresemann’s Bristlefront",
        "choice2": "Dryococelus australis",
        "choice3": "Land lobster",
        "choice4": "Tree weta",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "source":"",
        "question": "Which footballer has won the most trophies?",
        "choice1": "Vitor Bala",
        "choice2": "Ryan Giggs ",
        "choice3": "Dani Alves",
        "choice4": "Wael Gomaa",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "source":"",
        "question": " Which player has the most Champions League?",
        "choice1": "Paolo Maldini (AC Milan)",
        "choice2": "Francisco Gento (Real Madrid)",
        "choice3": "Alessandro Costacurta (AC Milan)",
        "choice4": "Cristiano Ronaldo (Manchester United, Real Madrid)",
        "answer": "2"
    }
]